hello everyone welcome back to another edition of this just in i am joined in the studio
as always with leonardo hello or well actually your first name is jorge yeah but uh it is very
difficult to pronounce for a lot of people why what did they say they say jorge or hey whore or
all right and you may hear some laughter in the studio we are also joined here with evan
hi how are you and claudia hello so evan and claudia are new to the office pod family they are
working as interns but in different departments yeah so a lot more of cafe makers now
yeah all right so claudia you're working in the marketing department yes i am what are you doing
there i'm doing marketing research for ross for ross how's ross as a boss hmm he i think
he's great yeah and it rhymes and it rhymes ross the boss well we'll have him in the studio soon
you know we always talk about ross he's uh he's in charge of marketing so he's a marketing manager
yeah so a lot of the promotions and stuff goes through him so we'll have him soon in the studio
he's from ireland so he's got a really cool accent he's grand he's grand all right and
evan is working with us at english pod right that's right i work with erica and marco to
help create the english pod lessons exactly so you might hear evan in a couple of our dialogues
in the supplementary vocab so don't be afraid it's just evan i don't bite where are you from evan
i'm from miami florida oh you're from florida too right yeah we're both from miami yeah did you
grew up together no are you brothers no there's two parts of miami there's the cuban side are
you boyfriend or girlfriend jewish side that's right way claudia that's right you have some
cuban heritage yes no completely cuban completely cuban no way no i'm an adopted cuban i am yes
i've never i've never listened to you speak spanish though wait wait so you were born in qua
no i mean my parents were both born in a Havana but both they came in the 70s so i was born here
i mean i'm not in the united states i mean there i go cool what about you you're saying that you're
an adopted cuban what i mean i grew up in miami so i you know grew up with the style grew up
with the food i'm jewish my whole family's jewish and i don't have any spanish you know heritage but
uh i kind of grew up and was raised in that atmosphere do you can you speak any spanish
my ex-girlfriend is cuban so excellent salsa dancer too nah i can do this also yeah so
are you the ex-girlfriend the cuban ex-girlfriend there's a lot of cubans so how do you know he's
a good salsa dancer oh because we've danced at the bulldogs yeah yeah that's a good excuse hey
yeah wow so salsa dancing now you know now you have somebody that competes against you dude i don't
dance any salsa i was gonna say you're like a superb salsa dancer okay i am i'm just shy i'm
just shy all right so we have a couple of things we want to talk about today why don't we start
with this week's lessons all right all right on monday we have a lesson coming up that's
about flattering somebody all right so yeah we're gonna teach you how to flatter someone you know
how to like give them nice compliments and make them feel nice give us a little example even
what you use to flatter somebody really depends on who you are trying to flatter i mean if you're
trying to flatter a teacher you know you would pretty much only talk about their ability to
teach you and you know they're how clear they are but if it was a girl you would want to
compliment their personality or their good looks how would you how would you flatter a girl how
would you how would you flatter claudia right here right now i'll tell you she has the most
gorgeous eyes
all right why are you flushing everyone's getting red here
can you can you blush no no they'll never blushes he's too much is it flush
blush it's blush it's blush all right so we're gonna be teaching you how to flatter someone and
on wednesday we have an advanced lesson where we're gonna be reviewing a movie so like movie
critics i love movies yeah what kind of movies all kinds i like you know depending on the mood
i like action comedy you know what about you claudia what type of movies are you in do you
like the girl flicks i like girl flicks i like mr you know what i like girl flicks too you do
yeah you do you like girl shows and flicks the occasional romantic comedies you know not that
you get to learn a lot about girls with those shows and the opposite sex come on yeah you're
the one watching sex in the city and getting advice from it exactly the city has a lot to
give to men really you see you see i haven't seen it but i heard that he's just not into you is a
pretty good movie um i went by myself to see that movie you really was my first solo experience
no way i've always wanted to do that but i've never been i know i didn't do it on purpose
it wasn't enough okay we can cut that out no it was no but just to explain it was my best
friend it's a girl she fell asleep on the couch and i got there and i was like i'm just gonna
watch it oh okay i thought you went to the movie theater oh yeah me too oh i did whoa whoa i did
she fell asleep so i tried calling her like where are you i'm trying to meet up with you
and she's like she's like not answering yeah exactly i got ditched to watch the movie he's
just not that into you i'm sure your friend wasn't sleeping uh that's an excuse make it a long way
she was just more into somebody else
i don't mind i'm not gonna lie all right and on friday we have our 100th lesson wow congratulations
so yeah we have 100 lessons i've been on 100 podcasts can you imagine that how many hours of
my voice have you heard already i don't know but i haven't heard anything in spanish i'm not
talking to you guys i'm talking to the users enough to recognize your voice anywhere
so what is that 100 lesson about well it's actually our 100th lesson we have Liliana
she's gonna be starring in that one and it's titled where are you from and what is she doing
there she's uh being herself you know kind of annoying no she's just arriving from a trip
somewhere because Liliana is always traveling so JP is a taxi driver and he's picking her up
like picking her up no like taking her to the hotel what no stop
all right so we're gonna be teaching you how to have this like small talk conversation with
the taxi driver which questions are appropriate to ask someone and which are not like for example
women get very annoyed when you ask them their age yeah yes so claudia how old are you i'm 21
21 what apparently she doesn't mind yeah you look like 30 no don't say how old are you
20 not five
26 almost almost all right so those are the three lessons coming up and it's time now for us to take
a look at the country of the week country so no more user of the week for now we're putting a pause
on user of the week we're going to have country of the week cool what country this week we have
russia as the country of the week russia mother russia nice and uh why why did they get this
did they send you a bottle of vodka no vodka comes from poland whatever i won't say why you say this
but i have my reasons all right so russia is the country of the week because we have
a lot of users from russia like we do from japan but actually not many users from russia comment
on the site we don't see many russians except for maxim maxim is the same thing last week
but you know what i said it and a couple of japanese already came out and started commenting
good for them that's great yeah yeah so now i hope that yeah these uh these other we have
a lot of users from russia they start in commenting because the only one that i know
is maxim maxim yeah the great the maxim the great right so uh hopefully yeah we'll get more
of these users to come out and and comments on the sites and and the lessons and yeah don't be shy
right can i leave my number for the russian girls no they're very pretty very pretty yeah yeah they
are actually they're they're very they're very tall and very attractive a lot of blondes yeah
you had a russian friend here before right yeah what happened um two left she went back to russia yeah
you know i thought it was really interesting uh when we went to hainan um there's like all in russian
all the signs are in russian because it's one of the closest beaches to russia so all of the russians
go to hainan and sanya off the coast of china to vacation especially especially in sanya and
wow there's a complete russian influence that i was there there's so many russians
let's go yeah let's go when um this weekend yeah okay so we're gonna go now we're gonna go to hainan
thanks everyone for listening we'll have our interns back soon and please come to our website
at englishpod.com leave your questions your comments and also sign up and you can listen
to these great lessons for a seven day free trial right that's right and if you're a russian you
have a house in hainan you can just uh tell us about this all the time we have for today so we'll
see you next time thank you bye bye peace